A Guide to the W. W. LaPrade and Brothers Records, 1803-2001 (bulk 1900-1970)
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Henrico County Vertical files, ca. 1920-1990 (bulk 1940-1970)., Extent: 23 boxes. (Box 8-30)
  - Subseries 4. Tuckahoe District., 7 boxes (7 cu. ft.)
    - Tuckahoe HT-30. (Box 20, Folder 27)
      Westham
    - Tuckahoe HT-30. (Box 20, Folder 28)
      Westham - Blocks A-B-C
    - Tuckahoe HT-30. (Box 20, Folder 29)
      Westham - Blocks D-E
    - Tuckahoe HT-30. (Box 20, Folder 30)
      Westham - Blocks G-H-I
    - Tuckahoe HT-30. (Box 20, Folder 31)
      Westham - Block J
    - Tuckahoe HT-30. (Box 20, Folder 32)
      Westham - Blocks K-L
    - Tuckahoe HT-30. (Box 20, Folder 33)
      Westham - Sections N-O
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-5. (Box 20, Folder 34)
      Murray Hill
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-6. (Box 20, Folder 35)
      Clovelly Gardens
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-8. (Box 20, Folder 36)
      Sterlingwood/Lindsay Place
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-8-1. (Box 20, Folder 37)
      Westham/Rollingham
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-9. (Box 20, Folder 38)
      West Forest Heights
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-9-3. (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
      Beverly Hills - Sections B-C-D-E
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-10. (Box 21, Folder 3)
      West University Heights
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-12. (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Ridgeway Farms - Sections C-D
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-14. (Box 21, Folder 5)
      Rivermont
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-15. (Box 21, Folder 6)
      Ridgecrest - Section 2
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-16. (Box 21, Folder 7)
      Ridgeview
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-A. (Box 21, Folder 8)
      Glenbrooke Hills; Roslyn Hills; River Road; River Hills; Forest Ridge; Sleepy Hollow; Countryside
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-B. (Box 21, Folder 9)
      Spottswood Park; University Heights; Glenridge, Rivermont
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-C. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-D. (Box 21, Folder 11)
      Forest Heights; Sunset Hills
    - Tuckahoe HT-30-E. (Box 21, Folder 12)
      College Terrace; Murray Hills; Three Chopt Court; Westhampton Hills; Lindsay Place; Rollingwood
    - Tuckahoe HT-31. (Box 21, Folder 13)
      Ridgecrest
    - Tuckahoe HT-31. (Box 21, Folder 14)
      Sheridan Hills
    - Tuckahoe HT-31. (Box 21, Folder 15)
      Westham Ridge; Briarfield
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-6. (Box 21, Folder 16-17)
      Greenbrier Hills
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-7. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      Moreland Farms
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-9. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      Sleepy Hollow Estates
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-12. (Box 21, Folder 20)
      Sleepy Hollow
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-13. (Box 21, Folder 21-22)
      Canterbury
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-13. (Box 21, Folder 23)
      Canterbury - Section 14
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-13. (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
      Canterbury - Mortgage Surveys
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-14. (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Drouin Hill
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-15. (Box 22, Folder 4-7)
      Westmoor
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-15. (Box 22, Folder 8)
      Wykehurst
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-16. (Box 22, Folder 9)
      Kingsley; Canterbury West
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-16. (Box 22, Folder 10-15)
      Gayton Crossing Shopping Center - Phase I
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-16. (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-16. (Box 23, Folder 3-7)
      Gayton Crossing Shopping Center - Phase II
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-A. (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
      Gayton Green - Sections A-B-C
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-A. (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
      Gayton Green - Section B
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-A. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-B. (Box 23, Folder 13)
      Bellefonte
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-B. (Box 23, Folder 14)
      Westhampton Cemetery
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-B. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-C. (Box 23, Folder 16)
      Pinnell Tract and Vicinity - Crescent Avenue
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-C. (Box 23, Folder 17)
      Reed Property
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-C. (Box 23, Folder 18)
      John Bates III - Highland Avenue
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-C. (Box 23, Folder 19)
      Ashby T. Wickham Estate
    - Tuckahoe HT-31-C. (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Tuckahoe HT-32-1. (Box 24, Folder 1)
      Tuckahoe Hills
    - Tuckahoe HT-32-2. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Westgate - York Realty Company - Skipwith Road
    - Tuckahoe HT-32-3. (Box 24, Folder 3)
      Michael Hills
    - Tuckahoe HT-32-4. (Box 24, Folder 4)
      Westdale Estates
    - Tuckahoe HT-32-5. (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Crestview
    - Tuckahoe HT-32-A. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Tuckahoe HT-32-B. (Box 24, Folder 7-11)
      Reynolds Metals
    - Tuckahoe HT-32-B. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Tuckahoe HT-32-C. (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Tuckahoe HT-32-D-1. (Box 24, Folder 14)
      Pine Dale; Pine Dell
    - Tuckahoe HT-32-D-2. (Box 24, Folder 15)
      Commerce Acres
    - Tuckahoe HT-35. (Box 24, Folder 16-17)
      Roxbury - Mortgage Surveys
    - Tuckahoe HT-35-1. (Box 24, Folder 18-19)
      Pinedale Farms
    - Tuckahoe HT-35-3. (Box 24, Folder 20)
      Three Chopt Estates
    - Tuckahoe HT-35-A. (Box 24, Folder 21)
      Colonial Court Apartments
    - Tuckahoe HT-35-B. (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Tuckahoe Misc. (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Country Day Care
    - Tuckahoe Misc. (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
      Henrico Sewer
    - Tuckahoe Misc. (Box 25, Folder 4)
      Jane Higgins - 908 South Gaskins Road
    - Tuckahoe Misc. (Box 25, Folder 5-8)
      Roxbury Outfall, Deep Run, Stony Run
    - Tuckahoe Misc. (Box 25, Folder 9)
      Safeway Store
    - Tuckahoe Misc. (Box 25, Folder 10-12)
      Tuckahoe Village; Canterbury
  - Subseries 5. Varina District., 4 boxes (4 cu. ft.)
    - Varina H-1. (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Colonial Court
    - Varina H-1. (Box 26, Folder 2)
      National Heights
    - Varina H-1. (Box 26, Folder 3)
      Richland Heights
    - Varina H-1. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Varina H-2. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Varina H-2. (Box 26, Folder 6-10a)
      Richmond Battlefield Park Corp.
    - Varina H-4. (Box 26, Folder 11)
      Deep Bottom Park
    - Varina H-4. (Box 26, Folder 12)
      Klotzek Property SW Corner Kingsland/WRVA Rds.
    - Varina H-4. (Box 26, Folder 13)
      Lone Star - Curles Neck
    - Varina H-4. (Box 26, Folder 14)
      Pickett River Estates Section A
    - Varina H-4. (Box 26, Folder 15)
      Phil Rutledge Parcel SW of Kingsland/Wallo Roads
    - Varina H-4. (Box 26, Folder 16)
      TARMAC Lonestar - Curles Neck/Route 5
    - Varina H-4. (Box 26, Folder 17)
      TARMAC Part Parcel 39-B2-2
    - Varina H-4. (Box 26, Folder 18-20)
      Tidewater Quarries - Reclamation Plan
    - Varina H-6. (Box 26, Folder 21)
      Yahley Mill Road, Turner Road, Hideaway Road (Cary A. Phillips)
    - Varina H-11. (Box 26, Folder 22)
      84 Lumber Co. & Jim Ellen Properties
    - Varina H-11. (Box 26, Folder 23-26)
      Audubon Crossing
    - Varina H-11. (Box 26, Folder 27)
      Bon Secours Richmond Health Systems
    - Varina H-11. (Box 26, Folder 28)
      CNB Branch Bank
    - Varina H-11. (Box 26, Folder 29)
      Commonwealth Square and Sheraton Inn
    - Varina H-11. (Box 26, Folder 30)
      First/Merchants Bank Laburnum/Finlay
    - Varina H-11. (Box 26, Folder 31)
      Laurel Pines Apartments
    - Varina H-11. (Box 27, Folder 1)
      Lynda Lane Townhouses - Bernstein
    - Varina H-11. (Box 27, Folder 2-6)
      Richmond Industrial Interport
    - Varina H-11. (Box 27, Folder 7)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - Allison-Erwin Co.
    - Varina H-11. (Box 27, Folder 8)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - Kraft Food & Central Virginia Food Bank
    - Varina H-11. (Box 27, Folder 8a)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - Media General
    - Varina H-11. (Box 27, Folder 9)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - National Starch and Chemical Corporation
    - Varina H-11. (Box 27, Folder 10-12)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - NARDI Warehouse/ Steve's Sash and Door
    - Varina H-11. (Box 27, Folder 13)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - Property at SE Corner Williamsburg/Klockner
    - Varina H-11. (Box 27, Folder 13a)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - Prudential Warehouse
    - Varina H-11. (Box 27, Folder 14)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - Purolator
    - Varina H-11. (Box 27, Folder 15)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - RPP Associates
    - Varina H-11. (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - "Silver" POD 106-88 Williamsburg/Klockner
    - Varina H-11. (Box 28, Folder 1a)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - Lowell Smith
    - Varina H-11. (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - "Young Phillips" for W.M. Saunders Lot 12-B
    - Varina H-11. (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - Lot 15-C-Sec. 2
    - Varina H-11. (Box 28, Folder 3a)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - Lot #37
    - Varina H-11. (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Richmond Industrial Interport - Individual Plats, etc.
    - Varina H-11. (Box 28, Folder 5)
      Richmond Memorial Hospital
    - Varina H-11-6. (Box 28, Folder 6)
      Goodrich Plaza Shopping Center
    - Varina H-12. (Box 28, Folder 7)
      Chrysler Realty Corporation
    - Varina H-12. (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Citgo - Nine Mile/Newbridge
    - Varina H-12. (Box 28, Folder 9)
      Coventry Gardens
    - Varina H-12. (Box 28, Folder 10)
      Fair Oaks Terrace
    - Varina H-12. (Box 28, Folder 11)
      Henrico Theatre - 305 E. Nine Mile Road
    - Varina H-12. (Box 28, Folder 12)
      Hershey Creamery Co. - 4110 Eubank Road
    - Varina H-12. (Box 28, Folder 13)
      KSB, Inc.
    - Varina H-12. (Box 28, Folder 14)
      Newbridge Shopping Center
    - Varina H-12. (Box 28, Folder 15)
      Newbridge Square Apartments (Rufus Blackburn)
    - Varina H-12. (Box 28, Folder 16)
      Newbridge Village Apartments - Hawkes Lane
    - Varina H-12. (Box 28, Folder 17)
      Pilot Oil Corporation
    - Varina H-13. (Box 28, Folder 18)
      Century Homes, Ltd. Trailer Sales Lot
    - Varina H-13. (Box 28, Folder 19)
      Charles City Road Water Main
    - Varina H-13. (Box 28, Folder 20)
      CSX - Lewis Road
    - Varina H-13. (Box 28, Folder 21)
      Gilmour Place (Ree Ellis)
    - Varina H-13. (Box 28, Folder 22)
      Lewis Gardens
    - Varina H-13. (Box 28, Folder 23-24)
      Mazo-Lerch
    - Varina H-13. (Box 28, Folder 25)
      Pilot Oil Corporation - 200 Williamsburg Road - Sandston
    - Varina H-13. (Box 28, Folder 26)
      Sternheimer (Old Ford Plant) Lewis/Ferncroft Roads
    - Varina H-13. (Box 28, Folder 27)
      Dr. Ruben Villaroman - 350 E. Williamsburg Road
    - Varina H-14. (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Lot 24 Fair Oaks Park - Jeff Bane, Jr.
    - Varina H-14. (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Green Meadows - Section D
    - Varina H-15. (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Ray Clarke - Windsor Road
    - Varina H-15. (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Gillen Property
    - Varina H-15. (Box 29, Folder 5)
      Riley Lowe - Chickahomony Swamp South of Bottoms Bridge
    - Varina H-16. (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Church's Fried Chicken
    - Varina HV-1. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Varina HV-2. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Varina HV-3A. (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Varina HV-3B. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Varina HV-3-1. (Box 29, Folder 10a)
      Richmond Battlefield Parks Corp.
    - Varina HV-4. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Varina HV-4-1. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Varina HV-6. (Box 29, Folder 12a)
    - Varina HV-13. (Box 29, Folder 13)
      Allstate/Inta-Roto
    - Varina HV-13. (Box 29, Folder 14)
      Ethyl Corporation - Byrd Airport - Lewis/Norman Roads
    - Varina Misc. (Box 29, Folder 15)
      Easco Photo Plant
    - Varina Misc. (Box 29, Folder 16)
      Ree Ellis
    - Varina Misc. (Box 29, Folder 17)
      Fotomat
    - Varina Misc. (Box 29, Folder 18-19)
      Hechler Village - K-Mart
    - Varina Misc. (Box 29, Folder 20)
      Linwood Toombs Trailer Park
    - Varina Misc. (Box 29, Folder 21)
      Seven Pines Elementary School
    - Varina Misc. (Box 29, Folder 22-25)
      Varina Middle School
  - Subseries 6. Miscellaneous., 1 box (1 cu. ft.)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 1)
      HB-16-1
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 2)
      H-20, Bryan Park Sewer
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 3)
      H-22-D, 4924 W. Broad St., Old Shelburn Transfer/Storage Building
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 4)
      H-23, B.E. Watts, 7621 Staples Mill Rd.
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 5)
      H-23, WRNL-WRXL, Bethlehem Rd.
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 6)
      HF-13, Sandston, Section E
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Brookfield Outfall
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 8)
      C & P Telephone, Cedar Fork at Nine Miles
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 9)
      Country Club of Virginia, James River Golf
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 10)
      Derbyshire Apartments
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 11)
      Phillips Service Station, I-64, Broad St.
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 12)
      West Broad St. Gardens, Lot #7 Block B
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 14)
      Westhampton Memorial Park
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Series III: Richmond City Vertical files, ca. 1920-1990 (bulk 1940-1970)., Extent: 13 boxes. (Box 31-43)
  This series includes plats and surveys, correspondence and deeds, relating to the city of Richmond. The more recent files, ca. 1980-1990, also include site plan applications, newspaper clippings, utility, sewer, and topographical maps, memos, soil evaluation reports, and building ordinances relating to the properties.
  The numbering system directly relates to the Index Keys created by LaPrade. Districts were imposed on the Richmond Index Keys by LaPrade. Consult the Keys to figure out the correlating number for the location. The collection is not organized chronologically so researchers looking for a specific survey must look in ALL boxes relating to Richmond.
  - Richmond A. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Richmond A. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Richmond A. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Fulton Hill Studio, old Robert Fulton School
  - Richmond A. (Box 31, Folder 3a)
    Harrison Place
  - Richmond B. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Capital City Iron Works
  - Richmond B. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Rocket's View
  - Richmond B. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Richmond B. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Richmond B. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Crown Central Petroleum Corporation
  - Richmond B-1. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Richmond B-1. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    G & T L.C., 20th and 21st streets
  - Richmond B-1. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    International Land Surveying Inc.
  - Richmond B-1. (Box 31, Folder 12-14)
  - Richmond B-B. (Box 31, Folder 15-17)
  - Richmond C. (Box 31, Folder 18-20)
  - Richmond C-1. (Box 31, Folder 21-25)
  - Richmond C-1. (Box 31, Folder 26)
    Bacon Retirement Community
  - Richmond C-2. (Box 31a, Folder 1-4)
  - Richmond C-2. (Box 31a, Folder 5)
    Waverly Place
  - Richmond D. (Box 31a, Folder 6-8)
  - Richmond D. (Box 31a, Folder 9)
    Fairmont Pool
  - Richmond D. (Box 31a, Folder 10)
    Harrington Row
  - Richmond D-1. (Box 31a, Folder 11)
  - Richmond D-1. (Box 31a, Folder 12)
    Alsal Corporation
  - Richmond D-1. (Box 31a, Folder 13)
    W.W. Grainger, Magnolia Rd.
  - Richmond E. (Box 31a, Folder 14-18)
  - Richmond E. (Box 31a, Folder 19-20)
    Lower Highland Elementary School
  - Richmond E. (Box 31a, Folder 21)
    Slurry Pavers Inc., Valley Rd.
  - Richmond E. (Box 31a, Folder 22)
    Willie Walker
  - Richmond E-1. (Box 31a, Folder 23)
    Green Park
  - Richmond F. (Box 31a, Folder 24-25)
  - Richmond F-1. (Box 31a, Folder 26)
  - Richmond G. (Box 32, Folder 1-4)
  - Richmond H. (Box 32, Folder 5-6)
  - Richmond H-1. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    DuVal's addition
  - Richmond H-23. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Hungary Springs Rd.
  - Richmond HV. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Virginia - North Carolina Wheel Co.
  - Richmond I. (Box 32, Folder 10-15)
  - Richmond I. (Box 32, Folder 16)
    Richmond Redevelopment and Housing Authority
  - Richmond I. (Box 32, Folder 17)
    VCU
  - Richmond I. (Box 32, Folder 18)
    YMCA - Franklin St.
  - Richmond I-1. (Box 32, Folder 19-24)
  - Richmond I-1. (Box 32, Folder 25)
    818, 824, and 826 W. Broad St.
  - Richmond I-1. (Box 32, Folder 26)
    1510 W. Broad St., Firestone Store
  - Richmond I-2. (Box 32a, Folder 1-4)
  - Richmond I-2. (Box 32a, Folder 5)
    1205-1223 School St., E.G. Bowles
  - Richmond I-2. (Box 32a, Folder 6)
    Richmond SPCA
  - Richmond J. (Box 32a, Folder 7-8)
  - Richmond J. (Box 32a, Folder 9)
    Kingsland Land Co.
  - Richmond J. (Box 32a, Folder 10)
    Rhoadmiller and Hermitage Rds.
  - Richmond J. (Box 32a, Folder 11)
    Richmond Natatorium Site
  - Richmond J. (Box 32a, Folder 12)
    VCU_ Track and Soccer Center Phase II
  - Richmond J-1. (Box 32a, Folder 13-15)
  - Richmond J-1. (Box 32, Folder 16)
    Beekne Inv. Co.
  - Richmond J-1. (Box 32a, Folder 17)
    Grace Covenant Presbyterian Church
  - Richmond J-1. (Box 32a, Folder 18)
    Pleasants Hardware
  - Richmond J-1. (Box 32a, Folder 19)
    Sears, Roebuck, and Co.
  - Richmond J-1. (Box 32a, Folder 20)
    Virginia Union University
  - Richmond J-2. (Box 32a, Folder 21)
  - Richmond J-2. (Box 32a, Folder 22-23)
    Crippled Children's Hospital (Children's Hospital)
  - Richmond J-2. (Box 32a, Folder 24)
    A.H. Robins
  - Richmond J-2. (Box 32a, Folder 25)
    Sherwood Park
  - Richmond J-3. (Box 33, Folder 1-4)
  - Richmond J-3. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Atlantic Electric Co.
  - Richmond J-3. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Brass Beds of Va., formerly Fruehoff Trailer Co.
  - Richmond J-3. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Marco Supply Co.
  - Richmond J-3. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    J.T. Mosick Jr., now ABC Store
  - Richmond J-3. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Rich-Mar Co.
  - Richmond J-3. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Seaboard Building employee parking lot
  - Richmond J-3. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    Seaboard Building
  - Richmond J-3. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    1601 Summit Ave.
  - Richmond J-13 through J-40. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Richmond K. (Box 33, Folder 14-16)
  - Richmond K. (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Richmond K. (Box 33, Folder 18-19)
    Union Theological Seminary
  - Richmond K-2. (Box 34, Folder 1-1a)
  - Richmond K-2. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    Old Brook Square
  - Richmond K-3. (Box 34, Folder 3-5)
  - Richmond K-3. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    Pine Camp Community Center
  - Richmond K-4. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    Rosedale
  - Richmond K-5. (Box 34, Folder 8-8b)
  - Richmond L. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Richmond L-1. (Box 34, Folder 9a-9c)
  - Richmond L-2. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Richmond L-2. (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Georgetown Apts.
  - Richmond L-3. (Box 34, Folder 12-13)
  - Richmond L-4. (Box 34, Folder 14-14a)
  - Richmond L-5. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Richmond L-5. (Box 34, Folder 16)
    Colonial Downs; Tracings in Big File Rich-L (oversize surveys)
  - Richmond L-6. (Box 34, Folder 17-19)
  - Richmond L-7. (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Richmond L-7. (Box 34, Folder 21-22)
    Willow Lawn Shopping Center
  - Richmond L-7. (Box 34a, Folder 1)
  - Richmond L-7. (Box 34a, Folder 2-3)
    Willow Lawn Sections 1 & 2; Formerly L-B1 and L-B2
  - Richmond L-8A. (Box 34a, Folder 4-6)
    The Village Shopping Center (previously Henrico County, Tuckahoe district 1-C)
  - Richmond L-8A. (Box 35, Folder 1-4)
    The Village Shopping Center Ukrops
  - Richmond L-8A. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    The Village Shopping Center
  - Richmond L-8A. (Box 35, Folder 6-7)
    The Village Shopping Center (water, sewer, wall, landscape)
  - Richmond L-8A. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Richmond L-8B. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    College View (also L-8H)
  - Richmond L-8C. (Box 35, Folder 10)
    Hampton Park
  - Richmond L-8D. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    Westhampton Heights
  - Richmond L-8E. (Box 35, Folder 12)
    Westhampton
  - Richmond L-8F. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    West View
  - Richmond L-8G. (Box 35, Folder 14)
    Monument Avenue Realty Co.
  - Richmond L-8H. (Box 35, Folder 15)
    College View (also L-8B)
  - Richmond L-8I. (Box 35, Folder 16)
    Hampton Park blocks A & B
  - Richmond L-8J. (Box 35, Folder 17)
    Westhampton Baptist, Pepper Ave., St. Christophers Rd.
  - Richmond L-8L. (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Richmond L-8M. (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Richmond L-9. (Box 35, Folder 20)
    Country Club of Virginia and surrounding areas
  - Richmond L-9. (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Richmond L-9. (Box 35, Folder 22)
    Rick Hood- Hood Properties subdivision
  - Richmond L-10. (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Richmond L-10. (Box 35, Folder 24-26)
    University of Richmond
  - Richmond L-10. (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
  - Richmond M. (Box 36, Folder 4-6)
  - Richmond M-1. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Richmond M-1. (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Belvidere Corp.
  - Richmond M-1. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Commonwealth Club
  - Richmond M-1. (Box 36, Folder 10)
    Baptist Board of Missions and Education
  - Richmond M-1. (Box 36, Folder 11)
    VCU- School of Engineering
  - Richmond N. (Box 36, Folder 12-13)
  - Richmond N-1. (Box 36, Folder 14-15)
  - Richmond O. (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Richmond O-1. (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Richmond P. (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Richmond P. (Box 36, Folder 19)
    Beirne subdivision
  - Richmond P. (Box 36, Folder 20)
    Citgo- Cary St.
  - Richmond P. (Box 36, Folder 21)
    CNB- Broad and Thompson St.
  - Richmond P. (Box 36, Folder 22)
    International Shopping Center
  - Richmond P-1. (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Richmond P-1. (Box 36, Folder 24-26)
    Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Confederate Home for Women, Center for Education and Outreach
  - Richmond P-1. (Box 37, Folder 1-3)
    Battle Abbey
  - Richmond P-2. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Richmond P-3. (Box 37, Folder 5-8)
    Kanawha Trace
  - Richmond P-3. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Richmond P-4. (Box 37, Folder 10-11)
  - Richmond P-5. (Box 37, Folder 12)
    Windsor Farms
  - Richmond P-6. (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Richmond P-6. (Box 37, Folder 14)
    Thalhimer properties, Locke Lane
  - Richmond P-6. (Box 37, Folder 15)
    White residence in Lock Green
  - Richmond P-6. (Box 37, Folder 16)
    400 Old Locke Lane
  - Richmond P-6. (Box 37, Folder 17)
    Science Center Foundation Lock Island
  - Richmond P-7. (Box 37, Folder 18-19)
  - Richmond P-7. (Box 37, Folder 20)
    Ralph May
  - Richmond P-7. (Box 37, Folder 21)
    Windemere Topo
  - Richmond Q. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Richmond Q-1. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Richmond Q-2. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Richmond Q-2. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Beacon's Press
  - Richmond Q-2. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    600 E. Broad St. (Project-I)
  - Richmond Q-2. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Richmond Coliseum
  - Richmond Q-2. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Virginia Biotechnical Parking Authority
  - Richmond Q-2. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    VCU Real Estate Foundation, VELA buildings
  - Richmond Q-3. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Richmond Q-3. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    CSX Property
  - Richmond Q-3. (Box 38, Folder 11)
    The PEL Corp.
  - Richmond Q-3. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    MCV North Hospital addition
  - Richmond Q-3. (Box 38, Folder 13-19)
    MCV, VCU
  - Richmond R. (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Richmond R-1. (Box 38, Folder 21)
    Broad/Grace Arcade
  - Richmond R-1. (Box 38, Folder 22)
    Reynolds Metal
  - Richmond R-1. (Box 38, Folder 23)
    The Richmond Ballet (formerly Reynolds Metal)
  - Richmond R-1. (Box 38, Folder 24-26)
    Richmond Newspapers Inc.
  - Richmond R-1. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Security Federal Savings and Loan Association of Virginia
  - Richmond R-1A. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Richmond R-1B. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Richmond R-2. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Richmond R-2. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    6th and Main - Main Street Center
  - Richmond R-2. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    Barret House
  - Richmond R-2. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    Franklin parking deck
  - Richmond R-3. (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
  - Richmond R-3. (Box 39, Folder 10)
    8th street parking log
  - Richmond R-3. (Box 39, Folder 11)
    MLH Realty Co.
  - Richmond R-3. (Box 39, Folder 12)
    Old VEPCO building
  - Richmond R-3. (Box 39, Folder 13)
    Ross building
  - Richmond R-3. (Box 39, Folder 14)
    St. Paul's Church